* * * Subs ripped by Europeside * * * Enjoy the show !
[ birds calling ]
You traveling with two sheilas , are you , mate ?
Uh , yep .
- Two , eh ? - Yep .
That 'll be a bit of fun , eh ?
Yeah , yeah .
Just sign there .
They get , uh , real easy when they travel .
Loosen up a bit , hey ?
Mate of mine reckons . He picks ' em up all the time .
Uh-huh .
- That 's it ? - Yep , yep .
Good on ya , champ .
Don 't do anything I wouldn 't do , eh ?
Nah. I won 't .
Send us a card .
All right .
[ starts engine ]
Fat fuck . What a tool .
[ women chattering ]
[ laughs ]
[ British accent ] How funny 's that ?
I like that . I think we should send that one .
[ British accent ] Do ya reckon ?
[ man ] Yep .
[ revs engine ]
Yep .
How long is this gonna take , mate ?
Not long .
How long 's not long ?
Well , I 've almost got it .
Yep .
- Yep . - Yep !
OK .
Yep .
Yep !
[ continues rewing engine ]
- Yep . - Yep .
He fancies you .
He doesn 't .
- Does . - You fancy him .
I don 't think so .
[ laughs ]
The three of us are going to be stuck in a car together for three weeks ,
and it 'll be trying enough without " is it me , or is he being weird today ? "
It 'd drive me barmy .
Yeah . You 're right .
He is cute , though .
Do you think he 's really got a girlfriend in Sydney ?
Why would he lie ?
He 's a bloke .
[ chuckles ]
I can 't believe we 're leaving .
I know .
It feels like two years , not two weeks .
[ horn blaring ]
[ male ] Whoo !
[ tires screech ]
Wow !
- Want a lift ? - [ woman ] I 'd love it .
I thought I requested purple .
Eh . For 1 , 500 bucks we 're lucky it 's got doors .
I love it .
Hey , where 's my stuff ?
We forgot about food for you . Sorry .
Yeah , we thought you 'd get by on our gratitude and appreciation .
[ laughs sarcastically ]
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
Where 's the booze ?
Oh , we 've made a decision .
After last night , never drinking again .
We 've got to get an early start
if we want to get to Wolf Oreek by tomorrow night .
Mm-hmm .
Piss off . Of course I checked .
[ chuckles ] How much of an organization Nazi is she ?
No , she 's right. ln bed by 9 : 30 .
[ all cheering ]
[ dance music ]
[ woman 1 ] This is bad , actually .
Oh !
[ woman 1 ] You weren 't gonna drink that . is that your beer ?
- Patrick . Pleased to meet you . - Nice to meet you .
That 's a pretty nice handshake there . Let 's give it a kiss .
Lovely , lovely .
- l can pack a punch . - You can pack a punch ?
Why would you want that ?
- l would if I had to . - [ Patrick ] lf you had to ? [ laughs ]
You gotta hear this bullshit story .
Bullshit ! It wasn 't bullshit !
[ shouting ]
Ten foot wave spraying ' .
Shh ! Shh !
[ laughter ]
[ cheering ]
[ dance music continues ]
Go on !
I think it 's past 9 : 30 .
[ all laughing ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ clinking , rattling ]
[ sighs ]
I got the worst taste in my mouth .
[ laughs ]
[ chattering indistinctly ]
[ * Daddy Oool3 Eagle Rock ]
[ guitar playing ]
* l 'd like to sing a song for you
[ stops playing ]
- OK , let me start again . - [ laughs ]
Here we go .
[ plays new song ]
- * l love her - Oh , God .
* l really , really love her
[ laughing ]
* Make me smile all the time
* When you cook my food and you clean my room
* l love you , Mum I love you , Mum
[ both women ] * He 's been playing guitar
* For a few weeks now
[ woman 1 ] * And he 's really , really , really crap
[ woman 2 ] * And he 's crap
[ woman 1 ] * Really shit
[ male ] * l 'm not that bad
[ woman 1 ] Oh , my God !
[ male ] Yeah , that 's cool .
That 's amazing .
You 're near the world 's fifth biggest UFO sighting area .
- [ male ] Kristy , I 'm serious . - l know !
- [ male ] I can hear you laughing . - What ? I 'm listening .
Fine .
- [ woman 1 ] I 'm listening . - [ Kristy ] Tell us .
Don 't listen to her . Tell me. I 'm listening .
All right. I read about this guy
who was driving out on the highway out there .
And he sees this light ahead of him , around 500 meters ,
and at first he thinks it 's a truck or a semi-trailer or something ,
'cause the light 's really bright , like glowing orange and shit .
- Yeah . - But as he gets closer ,
he realizes that the light 's about 10 meters off the ground ,
just hanging in mid-air .
So he 's scared , freaking out .
And then he hears this ... crack !
Like an explosion .
- That was supposed to scare us . - l know , it 's scary .
But he did . He heard this crack .
Like an explosion of a jet .
And itjust took off into the sky , straight up like a rocket .
And then as soon as it was gone ,
his carjust stopped in the middle of the road ,
and it was totally silent .
He was just sitting there , staring up at the stars .
In the middle of nowhere .
- Hey ... - No reason . Just stopped .
- ls that a true story ? - l read it .
You 've got something dripping off your lip there .
What ?
Oh , it 's all right . It 's just bullshit .
- No , bullshit you , mate ! - [ laughs ]
[ male laughs ]
What 's all this shit ?
- Oh , for the tent . - For the tent .
- Here , I 'll do that . Start on the tent . - No , you do the tent .
I don 't know what you two would do without me .
[ laughs ]
- l didn 't finish that . - Oh , sorry .
- This is it . - l finished it for you .
- What ? - l didn 't know what to do !
- All right ? - [ male ] Yep .
[ dog whines ]
Now we just got a six-hour drive . Who 's driving first ?
- Oh ! - Who 's driving first ?
I don 't know . I 'll go in the back .
- ls that all right with you ? - Yeah .
- l 'll go in the back . - Do you want to drive ?
[ squawking ]
[ car speeding ]
[ woman 1 ] We 're here , guys .
- [ male laughs ] - [ engine turns off ]
Well , well , well .
Hey , um , can I have the keys ?
[ laughs ]
Oh , it 's OK , you two. I 've got it .
Thanks . No problems , guys .
[ insect buzzing ]
[ whispering ] How 's the hair ?
Day one . Captain 's log .
So far , no sign of intelligent life forms .
Starting to doubt ... Hey .
- Howdy . - Howdy .
[ male ] Um , do you wanna say hello ?
- Hello . - [ chuckles ]
Righto . What 's your name ?
- Graham . - Graham .
Nice to meet you , Graham .
I 'm Ben .
- This one too ? - Yeah , man .
[ buzzing continues ]
I think someone 's got a crush on you .
Yeah , the attendant. I thought so .
- No . - Graham .
- Uh-uh . - Uh-uh .
I 'm getting the feeling it 's mutual . Am I wrong ?
[ chuckles ]
You know it 's true !
- Do you mind ? - You do !
I think it 's absolutely fabulous .
[ sighs ]
But don 't go dicking her around , because she 's totally brilliant .
If you hurt her , I 'm going to have to kill you .
So my advice is that we have an awesome time together .
You sort out whatever it is going on between you and this
so-called girlfriend you 've allegedly got .
By the time we get to Oairns , we 'll find some freakishly hot man for me ,
and we 'll all , you know , go crazy together , all right ?
All right . [ chuckles ]
She 's only a little one , isn 't she ?
I reckon I could break that in half real quickly , eh ?
Youse two 'd be watching me .
[ muttering indistinctly ]
- Here comes yours now , mate . - [ men laugh ]
What a place , huh ?
Hey , uh ... Hey , mate . Oi .
Oi . Hey , come here . I got a question for ya .
All right . You keep that .
How 're you going ?
Hey , uh ...
Me and me mates are gonna see
if your girlfriends would be interested in a little bit of a gang bang .
[ men laughing ]
We just want to make sure it 's all right with you first .
Good on ya . Fuckhead .
Hey , what 'd you say ?
I said ...
I said that 's , um ...
- ... a nice smile you got . - [ men laughing ]
Bazza , don 't be a dickhead .
- See you later , sweetheart . - [ men laugh ]
Bye .
[ men laughing ]
[ Ben ] Fucking assholes .
Bunch of morons . Honestly .
- Yeah . Forget about it , Ben . - No , I should 've smashed him .
- [ Ben ] I should 've T 'ai Ohi 'd his ass . - [ Kristy laughs ]
[ Ben ] I 'm serious .
[ men chattering ]
The weather 's shit .
Yeah . All of a sudden .
I think it 's the start of the wet season , so ...
[ woman 1 ] That 's beautiful over there , isn 't it ?
That light coming up through the mountains. lt 's gorgeous .
I hope it doesn 't rain .
[ Ben ] what ?
- l said I hope it doesn 't rain . - Man , it 's gonna be cold tonight .
I mean cold .
Great .
[ Kristy humming ]
Hey , I think that 's the start of it .
[ Kristy ] So it 's in there ? You 've got to climb over the top ?
Um , yeah .
- [ thud ] - Aw !
- [ woman 1 ] What was that ? - Rock .
[ women laugh ]
[ Ben ] There 's just nothing out here .
[ Kristy ] I know. lt 's great .
[ Ben ] Here we go . Wolf Oreek Orater !
- [ Kristy ] Orater ! We 're here ! - [ woman 1 ] Whoo !
[ all ] " Walking trail . "
- [ Ben ] " Allow , three ... Three hours . " - [ Kristy ] Three hours ?
is that three hours to get all the way to the middle or to get up to the top ?
- [ Ben ] I imagine it 's to the top . - [ woman 1 ] lt 's to the top .
[ Ben ] No camping . Hiking 's allowed .
Put rubbish in your bin and no fires . OK .
[ Kristy ] Right . Great . Let 's go .
- [ Ben ] Wow . Madame . - [ woman 1 ] Thank you .
- [ Ben ] Wolf Oreek awaits you . - [ woman 1 ] Oh , wow !
[ Ben ] Wolf Oreek !
Wow .
[ squawking ]
- lt 's a souvenir ... - [ shrieks ]
[ laughing ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
What is with this weather ?
- Maybe we should take an umbrella . - Yeah .
Yeah , definitely .
What do you want to take ?
- [ Kristy ] All of it . - [ woman 1 ] All what 's in the Esky .
- And who 's carrying all of this ? - [ woman 1 ] You are . [ chuckles ]
- [ Kristy ] Just all of it . - All right , three hours .
- Let 's do it ! - [ woman 1 ] Let 's go .
[ Ben ] Oh , wait .
[ Kristy ] Oh , there 's poo everywhere !
Yay ! We 're on the poo planet .
[ Kristy singing ]
[ woman 1 ] There 's another skull . Look .
They 're bones !
Oh , my God , there 's bones everywhere !
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Ben ] What are you doing ? It 's not raining that bad .
[ Kristy ] Yeah , it is . It 's freezing. I 've got no jumper .
- [ woman 1 ] Where did the meteorite go ? - [ Ben ] lt 's in the middle .
- [ woman 1 ] Just went into the ground ? - [ Ben ] Yeah .
Look how good it looks . Ooo-ooh !
Oome on !
Whoo !
Here .
You all right ?
[ woman 1 ] Wow . That 's impressive .
[ Ben ] You 're looking at one of the biggest meteorite craters on the planet .
They reckon the explosion from the impact
would 've been like 200 nuclear bombs going off at the same time .
Some guys discovered it scouting for an oil company in 1947 .
Imagine being the first person to see it .
Hey . Let 's go .
[ Ben ] You all right ?
[ rain falling ]
- This is great , Ben . - Yeah . Thank you .
It 's fantastic . Thank you .
Such a sweetheart , aren 't you ?
Loving it .
Yeah. lt 's great . [ laughs ]
[ Ben ] Sorry. I didn 't know .
It 'll clear . Give it a couple of hours .
[ Kristy ] Thank you .
Back soon .
Where are you going ?
I wonder why the meteor hit here .
In this place . Nowhere else .
[ thunder clapping ]
Maybe it was drawn to something in the Earth .
- Like when lightning strikes . - Hmm .
- Yeah ? - Hmm .
- Hi . - Hey .
[ Ben panting ] That 's awesome .
[ chuckles ]
[ both laughing ]
I was wondering what that would be like .
[ woman 1 ] Kris , what 's the time ?
Uh , don 't know . Watch has stopped .
It 's like Niagara Falls !
[ Ben ] Whoo !
[ shivering ]
- Hey , have you got the time ? - Nah. it 's busted .
I 'd say it 's about 7 300 . So about an hour till dark .
We 'll make it back to Halls Oreek , easy .
Kristy 's watch stopped too .
- Bullshit . Did it really ? - Yeah .
6330 . Mine too . [ laughing ]
What , batteries or something ?
[ woman 1 ] You got the keys ?
[ laughing ]
Make sure you warm her up first .
- [ Ben ] lt 's weird weather , eh ? - [ woman 1 ] Yeah , I reckon . God .
- [ keys jangling ] - [ Ben ] See you later , Wolf Oreek .
[ silence ]
- What 's wrong ? - l don 't know .
Did we leave the lights on ?
[ woman and Ben ] No .
is it ... is it in gear ?
- [ Ben ] No . Try ... Try again . - [ key turning ]
- [ silence ] - [ whispers ] Fuck .
- [ sighing ] - [ Ben ] OK .
[ Ben chuckles ] Shit .
Uh , pop ... Pop the hood .
It 's probably just the battery terminals .
[ Ben ] This one ...
[ muttering under breath ]
Do you know what you 're looking for ?
[ laughing ]
[ Kristy ] Oh ...
Are you gonna tell Liz ?
[ chuckles ] I 've got a feeling she already knows .
I 'll go see what I can do .
- [ mumbles ] - [ Kristy ] Did you hear that ?
- [ Ben ] You didn 't leave the lights on ? - No .
No .
Fucker .
Looks like we might be spending the night .
- This is fucked . - [ door slams ]
[ low ] Bitch .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ makes whooshing sounds ]
I am your father .
[ breathes noisily ]
[ sighs ]
[ Ben ] Do you think it means anything ?
I mean , the watches and the car not working .
- What do you mean ? - [ Ben ] Well ...
You know the stories I was telling you last night about the UFOs and stuff .
And when they were around ,
well , things stopped working .
[ Ben ] Oould be the same kind of thing .
Ben , I really don 't think we need to be talking about that right now .
OK .
There 's something out there .
- And it ain 't no man . - No , no. I saw some lights .
- [ Ben ] Where ? - Right ... Right there .
- [ Kristy ] There . - [ Ben ] What the hell ?
No , no , no . Don 't fucking ... What ?
- [ Kristy ] lt might be a car ! - Well , it might not be a car !
- [ Ben ] That don 't look like no car . - [ Liz ] Shit. lt 's coming this way .
Fuck , it is coming this way . Shit .
- [ Kristy ] Fuck ! - [ Ben ] Fuck. it is coming this way .
- Should we run ? - [ Ben ] No , no , no !
Just stay in the car ! Don 't move .
Hold on . Hang on , it 's a car .
[ Kristy ] How do you know ?
It 's a bloody car ! Shit !
- l can hear the engine . - [ car approaching ]
[ engine stops ]
What the bloody hell are you mob doing out here ?
- Scared the shit out of me . - [ all laughing ]
We thought it was aliens .
[ laughing ]
- Well , she did . - Hi .
It was pissing down with rain earlier . I was just about to chuck it in .
Lucky for you mob I decided to hang around a bit longer , eh ?
Yeah . We were just getting ready to spend the night too .
Ah , well . We 'll get you outta here quick smart .
Oome on , you bloody sparkplug !
- [ all laugh ] - Where ya heading ?
- Darwin , sort of . - Yeah , then on to Oairns .
- That 's where we 're really headed . - Long drive .
- Yeah . - lt 's too long .
- British , are youse ? - [ Liz ] Yeah .
- [ Kristy ] That 's right . - Ben 's an Aussie , though .
- Yeah ? Where ya from , mate ? - Sydney .
Poofta capital of Australia . [ laughs ]
- [ women laughing ] - Just playing with you , tiger .
Never been over there myself .
Lucky you sheilas are traveling with a bloke .
Oan 't be too careful .
[ man chuckles ]
- Ooh ! - Nothing wrong with the battery .
[ laughs ]
- l told you we 'd be all right . - l know . He 's hilarious .
He 's like one of those guys from the outback Australia shows .
- Yeah ! - Like Orocodile Dundee .
- [ Liz giggles ] - He 's a pisser .
You 're an Aussie . How come you don 't talk like him ?
You want the bad news ? Or the really bad news ?
Well , your coil 's rooted . Oactus . You 're not going nowhere .
- What can we do ? - Fuck. I had it totally checked ...
- Ben . Fuck . - [ Liz ] Must be something we can do .
You take the old one out , bung the new one in , Bob 's your sister .
The only good news is I got the gear to do it .
Problem is , it 's back at my camp just down the road a ways .
I 'm going back down there anyway ,
so I could give you a tow , fix it tonight .
Probably have you on the road by morning .
Otherwise , someone 'll be coming through here .
Eventually . [ laughs ]
Make up your mind , 'cause I gotta get a rattle on .
- [ Liz ] Thank you - [ Ben ] Thank you .
- What do you guys want to do ? - Might as well .
He 's not going to fix it for free , is he ?
What if he wants a couple hundred pounds or something ?
- A thousand , what ? I don 't know . - [ Ben ] OK , OK .
OK , first we gotta find out if he wants any money or not .
- l don 't have a lot of cash on me . - Me , neither .
Nor do I .
Duh .
Why don 't we get him to tow us to town , and we 'll get someone there ?
Yeah .
- OK . - Go on .
- You go on , you ask him . - l don 't want to .
Go on. lt 's a bloke thing . Go on .
Yeah , you must . Please ?
- Yeah . - lt 's a bloke thing .
[ Kristy ] Ask him .
- [ Ben ] You didn 't need any help ? - Nah , I 'm all right . Thanks , though .
Oertain way of putting it in .
Um , I know it 's a long way , but the girls were wondering
if you could tow us back into town .
I mean , we don 't wanna put you out any more than we already have .
Look , I 'd really like to help you , mate ,
but I 'm not heading that way , you know ?
If you don 't want the lift , that 's up to you , but I 'm heading south .
- South . - Yeah , south .
South .
- You wanna go north . - Yeah .
- l 'm heading south . - [ both chuckling ]
Yeah .
- Bit of a bugger . - Bugger . Yeah .
[ Ben ] So , um ...
- Well , with that coil ... - Yeah ?
... and stuff ...
How much would that cost , say if we just got you to do that ?
It 's not fuckin ' Pitt Street , mate !
Of course I 'm not gonna charge you , you stupid bastard ! Hey ?
[ laughs ] You hear that ? " How much ? "
Hey ?
- [ Ben ] Oh , you sure ? - Oh , Jesus , you make me laugh .
You must keep the little buggers amused , hey ?
[ Ben ] Yeah .
You amuse the bloody bejesus out of me .
All right. I 'll get the girls going .
- That 'd be a good idea . - Yeah , good idea .
- Off you go . - Off I go .
Yay .
All right .
[ sighs ]
Where did he say his place was again ?
South .
It feels like we 've been driving for hours .
We shouldn 't be too far .
That 's what you said an hour ago .
OK , let 's just get him to drop us off here then , all right ?
It 's cool .
He said it was gonna be a bit of a drive , didn 't he ?
Mm-hmm .
It 's cool .
Must be some sort of mining operation .
[ Ben ] Hmm . Looks like a ghost town .
- We 're here . - Thank God .
Wherever here is .
- [ man ] I have plenty of water there . - [ Liz ] Aw , thank you .
It 's the one thing that we don 't have plenty of .
[ Ben ] Oheers .
Nothing like rainwater from the top end .
Hey , Mick , this place is amazing .
I can 't believe they just walked out and left all this stuff here .
Plenty of places like this all over the outback .
Thousands of ' em . Places people 've forgotten about .
[ Mick ] Must be a whole town out there somewhere .
Got lost in a six-month dust storm back in the ' 40s .
The people just walked away .
I heard of blokes gettin ' lost on their own farms .
Just never found their way out .
- On their own property ? - Mm-hmm .
That 's amazing .
Oh , there 's one up here that crosses three states , right ?
- Takes six days to drive across . - No !
I ... I ... We used to work out there once .
- What 'd you do there ? - Head shooter .
You know , clearing ' vermin .
Roos , horses , pigs , buffalo . You name it .
Don 't work there no more .
Use poisons . You know , instead of shooters .
Yeah , used to ... used to fly in with the helicopters .
[ stuttering ] You fly in low over a herd of water buffalo .
Sometimes take out 50 head in an afternoon .
I wore out five bolts on a .303 one year .
Pigs . Pigs were different . You have to get in close .
Get the dogs onto ' em , and then you go in with a knife .
You had to get in under him , you know , while the pig 's fighting off the dogs .
And you had to be quick .
Otherwise , you 'd lose your guts on its tusk .
- Sharp ! - [ chuckles ]
I seen a big boar pig , right ?
Take a pitbull 's head clean off one time .
[ makes whooshing sound ]
Little legs still pumpin ' away . [ makes squirting sound ]
Oh !
- [ Mick ] Fair dinkum . - Fair dinkum ?
That 's what I said , yeah .
[ chuckling ] Fair dinkum .
Wow . Poor little fella .
[ all laugh ]
- So , um , where do you live ? - Oh , I get around , you know .
Never know where l might pop up .
[ laughs ]
- Man , you must love the freedom . - What ?
The freedom . You know , you must love it .
You know , hangin ' out in nature and shit .
- [ Mick ] Right . - [ Ben ] Yeah .
[ Ben ] You get to , like , you know , cruise around the bush .
Saying cool stuff like , " that 's not a knife , this is a knife . "
[ both laugh ]
[ Ben ] You know what I 'm talking about ? Yeah ?
What do you actually do ... now ?
Oh , I could tell ya , but then I 'd have to kill ya .
[ laughs ]
So you don 't really shoot kangaroos , do you ?
I 'm doing people a service by taking out a few roos .
They 're everywhere out here now .
Like tourists .
[ all laughing ]
[ belches ] Oh . Excusez moi .
[ belches loudly ]
- Oi . - [ belches ]
Oi . Your turn .
[ farts ]
[ all laugh ]
Fair go .
Bloody women here , son .
Well , um , I 'll let you know when I get it goin ' . What do ya reckon ?
- Thank you . - [ Mick ] No worries .
- Thank you . - [ Ben ] Thanks .
[ Ben yawns ]
" But then I 'd have to kill ya . "
Shh .
What ?
Did you see the way he was looking at you ?
He 's trying to impress us with his great white hunter thing .
But he 's doing us a favor . He probably doesn 't appreciate us
cracking jokes at his expense . Seriously .
- [ Liz ] Let 's get the car fixed . - That 's what we 're doing .
Don 't freak out .
- [ Mick ] You all right ? - Fine , thanks .
Thanks again for helping us out .
No worries .
Obviously , it 'd be great to get going as soon as possible .
Ben .
Ben , move the Esky away from the fire .
[ sighing ] Ben .
[ gasping ]
[ panting ]
Oh !
[ whimpering ]
[ sobbing ]
[ panting ]
[ moaning ]
[ glass shard falling ]
[ gasping ]
[ distant scream ]
[ Kristy ] No !
No ! Aah !
[ screaming continues ]
[ man speaking indistinctly on radio ]
[ breathing shallowly ]
[ radio static ]
[ screaming hysterically ]
Please don 't kill me .
Please .
[ Kristy ] Please ! Aah !
Please !
Don 't kill me ! Please !
[ Kristy ] No !
Don 't kill me !
Bang !
[ Mick laughing ]
[ screaming hysterically ]
[ chuckles ]
Well , nothing happens when the bolt 's open , you see ?
[ laughs ]
[ rifle clicks ]
Uh-oh !
[ Kristy shrieking ]
[ screaming ]
[ Mick laughing ]
The look on your fuckin ' face !
[ Kristy ] Why are you doing this ?
Why ?
Please ! If you let me go , I won 't tell anyone .
- Shh , shh , shh . - [ Kristy ] I won 't ! I won 't !
Oome on . Oalm down .
Listen to Uncle Michael .
Oome on .
[ Mick ] Now , as I keep tellin ' ya ,
you know , I always use a rubber with you cunts .
[ Kristy screams ]
- l don 't know where you been . - [ screaming ]
Fuck you !
[ Mick ] Mmm .
Mmm !
[ Kristy ] Get away from me !
Fuck you !
Fuck you , cunt !
No !
Aah !
[ spitting ]
Fuck you , cunt !
You fucking loser !
You fucking loser .
Thank you very much .
You know ...
You know how I know that you 're not gonna tell nobody ?
You know how I know ?
No ! No !
[ Mick ] Off with your little pinkies .
[ Kristy continues screaming ]
Fuck !
[ air hissing ]
[ Kristy screaming ]
Ah !
[ Mick ] Jesus Ohrist , Mick !
Rule number one . Put the bloody fire out .
For fuck 's sake !
[ Mick ] Bloody hell !
[ muttering ]
Shh ! Kristy !
- [ shrieking ] - Shh ! Shh !
Please ! Shh !
[ sobbing ]
Shh ! Shh !
Where 's Ben ? Where 's Ben ?
Shh . Kristy , you have to be quiet .
Shh !
Oh . You 're still awake , are ya ?
You know , a man 's a real goose , eh ?
I mean , it took four hours
to get those fuckin ' parts out of your car , right ?
Now the bastard thing 's all burnt .
What do ya think of that ?
[ sobbing ]
[ Mick groaning ]
Bloody this , all .
Now ...
Where were we ?
Eh ?
Oh , yeah .
Let 's play . Hey ?
[ chuckling ]
[ Mick grunting ]
[ Mick ] You like to play , don 't ya ?
You like to play , hey ? Hey ? Hey ?
You like to play , do ya ? Hey ? Hey ?
That stupid bitch over there . See that stupid bitch over there ?
She loved it .
While she lasted . Good few months .
We were great together , you know ?
Till she lost her head !
[ panting ]
- [ banging ] - [ groaning ]
- [ Kristy panting ] - How about ...
How about I cut your tits off , hey ?
Out your tits off .
You 're all the same , you foreign cunts .
Weak as piss .
[ rifle cocks ]
[ Kristy laughing ]
Now , how the hell did you get out ?
You 're wasting your time , eh ?
It 's not loaded . I only put one up the spout .
[ stuttering ] Let her go .
Now !
Get away from her !
Now , Lizzy .
Now , a rifle in the wrong hands can be , you know , really dangerous .
- So , give me the fuckin ' ... - [ gunshot ]
[ groaning ]
[ muffled ] Kill him !
[ rifle clicking ]
Kill him !
No !
[ yelling ]
[ Kristy sobbing ]
[ Kristy ] Please help me .
[ Liz ] Oome on .
No ! No !
Where are you going ?
Don 't go !
[ sobbing ]
[ Kristy ] Yes !
[ engine starts ]
[ rewing ]
[ laughing ]
[ groaning ]
- [ rewing ] - Hang onto something !
Go !
Oome on !
Go , go , go , Liz !
[ indistinct , whimpering ]
[ Kristy ] Go , go !
[ engine dies ]
[ both panting ]
[ hysterical chuckling ]
[ Liz ] Oome on .
- Push ! - What ?
He 'll see the lights go over !
[ both straining ]
[ crashing ]
[ Kristy laughing ]
- Follow me . - Are you joking ?
[ Liz ] Oome on .
[ car approaching ]
[ engine turns off ]
[ car door opens ]
[ car door shuts ]
[ rustling ]
He 's going to check on us .
Let 's go .
[ gasping ]
Fuck !
He killed that person back there .
Did you see Ben ?
She 'd been alive for months .
We 've got to move .
- He 's going to do that to us . - We can 't go that way .
- He 's gonna see we 're not down there . - l know , I know !
I 've got a set of keys .
- He must have more cars . - l 'm not going back there .
We 're in the middle of fucking nowhere . We need a car .
Oome on .
[ Kristy ] Wait . Wait .
- Wait . - You all right ?
I just gotta catch my breath . Wait .
- You OK ? - Yeah .
It 's all right. lt 's all right .
[ coughs ]
- [ panting ] - Listen , Kris .
You 're just gonna have to wait here for a minute , all right ?
No !
- No ! - Listen , it 's just for five minutes .
- Please , don 't leave me . Please ! - Listen .
- What if he catches me again ? - He won 't , he won 't .
Please , don 't leave me !
He 's not going to catch you again , all right ?
You just have to wait here for five minutes , OK ?
I 'll be in and out . I 'll be quicker on my own , OK ?
Listen .
[ Liz ] Look ...
lf l 'm not back , all right , in five minutes ,
just head that way , OK ?
And you 'll hit a road eventually , all right ?
I 'll catch up with you .
OK. I 'm quicker on my own . All right ? I 'm coming back .
- OK ? - Wait .
- Please . - Five minutes .
It 's OK . It 's all right .
- [ sobbing ] Don 't go ! - lt 's all right .
What if he catches me again ?
He 's not ... He 's not gonna ...
He 's not gonna catch you again , all right ?
Listen .
Listen , you just wait here , all right ?
[ sobbing ] Please hurry .
[ gasping ]
[ barrel spins ]
[ metal crashing ]
Shit !
Oh , God .
[ grunts ] Uhh !
Uhh ...
Ahh !
[ screaming ]
[ continues screaming ]
[ whispering ] Ben ?
[ breathing heavily ]
Ben .
[ woman ] lt 's excellent . Yeah , I 've never seen better .
Bella , bella , belial
I 'm sure we did . I thought we got this fixed .
- Honey , I 'm not in the mood , all right ? - [ woman groans ]
- [ Mick ] How 's it going , mate ? - Not too good .
[ man ] What do you expect ?
He 's from the country . That 's what happens .
Country people are friendly , though .
[ Mick speaking indistinctly ]
- Thirsty , are ya ? - Yeah .
Eh ? Nothing like rainwater from the top end .
So far , no sign of intelligent life forms .
Um , do you wanna say hello ?
- Righto . What 's your name ? - Graham .
Graham . Nice to meet you , Graham .
I 'm Ben .
- This one too ? - Yeah , man .
[ panting ]
[ keys jingling ]
[ engine faltering ]
[ engine starts ]
[ Mick laughs ]
[ grunting ]
- Ah ! - [ Liz gurgling ]
[ moaning ]
[ sobbing ]
[ Mick laughing ]
Hey .
Like your little mate said before , you know .
[ Mick ] That 's not a knife .
This is a knife .
[ screaming ]
[ Mick ] Now , come on . Oome on , Lizzie .
Oome on !
Settle down , you know .
That 's not gonna kill ya . All right ?
I got a bullet hole in me neck and I 'm not whingeing , am I ? No .
[ screaming ]
I 'm gonna have to do something , Lizzy .
So as you don 't try and run out on me , you know ?
It 's ... It 's a little trick they used to use in the Vietnam War , you know ?
So they could take prisoners
and they still get the same information out of ' em .
But the little buggers didn 't escape . You with me ?
You with me ?
- You see what I mean ? Eh ? - [ screaming ]
No ! No !
Now that !
That 's for fuckin ' wreckin' me fuckin ' truck , you bitch !
[ wheezing ]
Now , this little procedure
is called " making a head on a stick . "
Because once your spine 's severed , right ...
[ Liz ] No !
[ gasping ]
That 's what you are , hey ?
Head on a stick . [ laughs ]
Now ...
Let 's talk about your little mate , um , Kristy .
[ whispering ] Liz .
Liz .
[ panting ]
[ gasping ]
[ wheezing ]
[ car approaching ]
[ gasping ]
What happened ?
[ sobs ]
Jesus .
I 'll get a blanket . Get you some help .
[ distant gunshot ]
[ gunshot ]
[ thud ]
[ breathing heavily ]
- [ retching ] - [ insects buzzing ]
No ! No !
[ moaning ]
Oh !
[ engine faltering ]
[ screeching ]
[ rewing engine ]
[ engine turns over ]
[ engine rewing ]
Oome on ! Move !
[ rewing ]
[ tires screeching ]
Oome on ! Oome on !
Oome on ! Fucking move !
Move ! Oome on ! Fuck !
Oome on !
No ! No , no !
[ sobbing ] No .
Fuck you ! Fuck you !
Asshole !
Oh , fuck ! No !
[ laughing hysterically ]
[ engine dies ]
[ cocks rifle ]
The winner !
[ car approaching ]
- [ gunshot ] - [ muffled groan ]
[ Mick sniffs , clears throat ]
[ gunshot ]
[ wheezing ]
[ gasping ]
[ loud barking ]
[ screaming ]
[ coughing ]
[ panting ]
[ barking continues ]
[ wheezing ]
[ Ben ] Help !
[ screams ]
[ sobbing ]
[ speaking German ]
[ rumbling ]